<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Family and Financial Therapy</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Family and Financial Therapy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Jean Theurer</title>
      <link>/team/jean-theurer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/jean-theurer/</guid>
      <description>Pyschology Today I specialize in helping individuals, couples, and families develop healthy, happy, and successful relationships. My approach is influenced by your specific needs, goals, and life circumstances.
I endeavor to create a supportive therapeutic environment where you feel heard and understood so you can engage in meaningful exploration of the issues that are impacting your well-being. Through therapy, I believe your relationships with yourself, your family and loved ones, and your money can improve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>⠀</title>
      <link>/team/zeducation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/zeducation/</guid>
      <description>   PhD in Counselor Education, 2015
University of Florida
    Masters in Business Administration, 1983
The Wharton School, University of Pennsylvania
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Couples Therapy</title>
      <link>/services/couples-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/couples-therapy/</guid>
      <description>Learn the habits of healthy, happy, and successful couples.
Most of us learn about relationships from trial and error, our families and friends, or from the media. These role models may not pass on the skills that are necessary for healthy, happy, and successful relationships.
Fortunately, there are many effective counseling theories and interventions which have been developed and tested with evidence-based research. Here are a few therapeutic approaches that you may find interesting and applicable to the challenges you are facing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Therapy</title>
      <link>/services/family-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/family-therapy/</guid>
      <description>Invest in your relationships.
Whether you come alone or with the whole clan, family therapy can help you make the changes in your relationships that you desire. Small changes in how you interact with your family members can profoundly impact their interactions with you.
There are many reasons for a family to be unhappy and disconnected. There are many transitions in the family life cycle that may create challenges (having children, adolescent and teen years, aging parents, illnesses, loss, divorce, financial struggles).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Therapy</title>
      <link>/services/financial-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/financial-therapy/</guid>
      <description>A newly emerging field that integrates mental health therapy with financial planning.
As a licensed therapist and certified financial planner, I am trained to help you understand the cognitive, emotional, behavioral, and relational aspects of your emotional and financial health.
Money is woven deeply into almost every aspect of our lives. Sometimes financial knowledge is all that is needed to improve your financial circumstances. However, even the decisions of the savviest financial guru are affected by emotions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Individual Therapy</title>
      <link>/services/individual-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/individual-therapy/</guid>
      <description>Your relationship with yourself is at the core of your happiness.
It is also the foundation for all your other relationships whether with your family and loved ones, or your money. Yet, it is the one relationship that most people ignore.
Individual therapy can help you become the person that you want to be by whittling away the habits that you want to eliminate, nurturing the parts of you that you want to grow, and developing new ways of handling life&amp;rsquo;s joys and challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Coaching</title>
      <link>/services/life-coaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/life-coaching/</guid>
      <description>Navigate changes in your life with clarity and confidence.
Every life stage brings changes. Some changes are painful, exhausting, and scary. But, sometimes they also give rise to opportunities.
Life coaching provides the mentoring, tutoring or accountability you need to grow and accomplish your goals. ​ It is a collaborative process that takes you from where you are now and moves you toward what you really want in life, helping you to create a life you love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Take the first step To learn more about how we can work together to help you have the relationships you desire, contact Dr. Jean Theurer for a free 15-minute phone consultation.
Call 352-641-0239 or email: Info@FamilyandFinancialTherapy.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faqs/</guid>
      <description>What can I expect when I start therapy? Since therapy requires considerable time, effort, and money. it is essential that we have a mutually shared understanding about the process of therapy. Typically, the first few sessions are dedicated to getting to know one another. During this time, we will work collaboratively to design some possible paths for you to achieve your goals for therapy.
By tailoring my approach to meet your unique needs, cultural background, and life circumstances, I endeavor to create a warm, supportive therapeutic environment where you feel heard and understood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forms</title>
      <link>/forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/forms/</guid>
      <description>On this page, you will find the forms you need to complete before we meet. Please download the forms if you have completed the initial free 15-minute phone consultation. To schedule a phone consultation, go to the Contacts page and send an email or call the office.
Please fill out these forms carefully and ask any questions you may have about them. Bring the completed forms to our intake meeting as we will not be able to proceed until these forms are completed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In The Press</title>
      <link>/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/press/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Jean Theurer is featured on BBC Money &amp;amp; Power: The Currency of Life. She counsels couples as they talk honestly and openly about money. The couples explore where their entrenched attitudes about spending and saving come from and how these attitudes affect their relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>